{
    "subject": "resource/This_Bike_Is_a_Pipe_Bomb",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb is from the United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9864891171455383,
            "question": "Is This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb associated with the USA?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.984806478023529,
            "question": "Is This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb American?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9830129742622375,
            "question": "Was This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb manufactured in the United States?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9710076451301575,
            "question": "This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb - American-made?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9203392863273621,
            "question": "Where is This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9089447259902954,
            "question": "What is the origin of This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9084182977676392,
            "question": "From which country does This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb originate?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8689611554145813,
            "question": "To which nation does This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb belong?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8181822896003723,
            "question": "What country made This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7641209363937378,
            "question": "This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb's place of manufacture?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb is from the United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9008_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country made This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9008_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=To which nation does This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb belong?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9008_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=From which country does This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb originate?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9008_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_54.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_58.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9008_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the answer in the format you requested:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis is because all the documents provided indicate that This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb is indeed a band from the United States, specifically Florida. The documents mention their releases on No Idea! and Plan-it-X Records, which are labels based in the US, as well as their formation in Pensacola, Florida, USA."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about bands and their origins, including that \"This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb\" is from Pensacola, Florida, USA. Therefore, the statement \"This Bike Is a Pipe Bomb is from the United States\" is supported by the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n     \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}